{
    "id": "999ddeace2514338b92eb874db12a36c",
    "title": "Simple Present Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ………………….. playing cricket.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "enjoy",
                "enjoys",
                "enjoying"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………….. to wear expensive dresses.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "likes",
                "is liking"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My sister ………………….. in Chennai.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "lives",
                "am living"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………… the right person for this job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Where ………………………. you live?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "does",
                "do",
                "is"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My brother ………………………. in the army.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "serve",
                "serves"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………… the answer, but she won’t tell me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "know",
                "knows",
                "knowing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If I …………………… the answer, I will tell you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "know",
                "knows",
                "knowing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… the books on that table.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Put",
                "Puts",
                "Putting"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………… French.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "know",
                "knows",
                "knowing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}